hey everybody i want to thank you all
for helping me reach 100 000 subscribers
it's pretty cool that this channel has
reached that many people to celebrate
100 000 subscribers i wanted to do a
special video talking about the
techniques that i use for my listening
practice in my own language learning so
i want to give you a few quick listening
tips based on my own language learning
experience and i'll give each tip in a
different language
content
is
my last tip for you is to challenge
yourself if you only listen to content
that you already understand almost 100
of then you're not going to improve much
so for example if you listen to my
podcast and you already understand
almost everything without using the
transcript then it's time for you to
start using more advanced content this
is why i created my advanced podcast so
you can train with real fast english in
my advanced episodes i speak at normal
speed so it's more difficult than the
normal listening time podcast but i
provide the transcript which will help
you understand what i'm saying so
remember you need to challenge yourself
if you want to reach a higher level of
listening alright i hope these tips were
helpful for you if you need help to
improve your listening skills then join
my membership so you can receive my
specialized training and if you want my
advanced podcast episodes that i
mentioned then become a listening time
family member click on the link in the
description below this video to sign up
today thank you all for helping me reach
100 000 subscribers and i wish you all
the best with your english learning